It's been a while.
久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気してた?
yes.
はい
The atmosphere has changed somehow.
なんか雰囲気変わったね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's getting really cute.
すごい可愛くなってる
Shall we move for now?
とりあえず移動しようか
Have you recently moved to this area?
この辺に最近引っ越してきたの?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Is it easy to live?
住みやすい?
Around here?
この辺?
I agree.
そうですね
Because there are various things.
いろいろあるから
It's easy to live in.
住みやすいです
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
I was wondering what happened when I got the call suddenly.
急に連絡を受けたから どうしたのかなと思って
Since I moved nearby, I thought I'd like to see you again.
近くに引っ越してきたので また会いたいなと思って
I'm so happy.
めっちゃ嬉しい
That's terrible.
やばいね
I was just thinking about contacting you too.
ちょうど俺も連絡しようかなと思ってて
Is it true?
本当ですか?
The timing was really good, so I got really excited.
タイミングめっちゃ良かったから めっちゃテンション上がっちゃ
There it was.
いました よ
That's right.
そうなんだ
I guess I'll stop by a convenience store and go home anyway.
とりあえずなんか コンビニでもよって 家に行こうか
got it.
わかりました
Well then, for now.
じゃあもうとりあえず
let's go.
行こう
It's this way.
こっちだね
No, but it's been a really long time.
いやでもマジ久しぶりだね
About a year?
1年くらい?
Were there that many?
そんなにいた?
That might be it.
それくらいかもしれないです
That's right.
そうだよね
The color of your hair is really nice.
髪の色めっちゃいいね
So wonderful.
すごい素敵
I feel more like an adult now.
なんか大人っぽくなったね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
How have you been lately?
最近どうなの?
Work or something.
仕事とか
It's still going well.
まだも順調です
Seriously?
マジで?
Last time we met, we were having a lot of troubles about work and relationships.
前会った時さ 結構なんか 仕事のこととかで 人間関係とか悩
You were talking about something like that.
んで るみたいな 話してたじゃん
I'm doing my best.
頑張ってます
Are you continuing your previous job?
前の仕事続けてるの?
still.
まだ
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's great, I guess.
えらいね、なんかね
I'll be arriving soon, so let's talk some more there.
もうすぐ着くからちょっと じゃあそこで話もうちょっと聞か
Let me.
せて
yes.
はい
Anyway, again.
と りあえずまた
It's been a really long time.
ほ んと久しぶりだね
For now, let's open the one I bought at the convenience store.
とりあえずコンビニで買ってきたやつ開けようよ
yes.
はい
What did you buy?
何買ったの?
I bought vegetable sticks.
野菜スティック買いました
It's cute.
可愛いね
Is that enough?
それで足りる?
I didn't buy any alcohol, is that okay?
お酒とか買ってこなかったけど大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Is that what you eat?
そんな消食だっけ?
I am on a diet.
ダイエット中です
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
There's no need to lose that much weight.
そんな痩せる必要ないって
Didn't you buy green onions?
おネギ買わなかった?
yes.
はい
Well, it's totally fine to eat.
まあ、全然いいよ食べても
thank you.
ありがとうございます
No, seriously, it's been a while and I'm super happy.
いや、まじで久しぶりに過ぎて 超嬉しい
It's been a really long time.
めちゃめちゃ久しぶり
That's right.
だよね
Why did you contact me?
どうして連絡くれたの?
You said earlier that you felt lonely.
なんか寂しいみたいなことさっき言ってたけど
I agree.
そうですね
I remembered her and wanted to meet her, so I contacted her.
思い出して会いたいなと思って連絡しました
Wait, do you have a boyfriend or something now?
え、彼氏とかは今いるの?
He's not there even now.
今もいないです
Huh, all the time?
え、ずっと?
I came in the middle of the day, but I'm already home.
途中で来たけどもう帰りました
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Eh, why did you break up?
え、なんで別れちゃったの?
Well, various things.
えー、いろいろ
various?
いろいろ?
No, isn't that boyfriend a waste?
いや、その彼氏もったいなくない?
After all, the personality of such a cute person is also great.
だって、こんな可愛い人の性格もいいかなんて
Even if you search all over the world, you won't find it.
世の中探してもなかなかいないよ
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
So, are there no good people or anything like that now?
じゃあ、今いい人とかそういう人もいないの?
He's not there right now.
今はいないですね
That's right.
そうなんだ
What, you didn't eat at all?
え、全然食べなかったの?
I don't eat.
食べない
I'd like to find a place to meet someone, or a meeting place.
そういう出会いの場とかさ、 待ち合わせやってみたいとか、
Isn't there such a thing?
そういうのとかもないの?
Yeah, I feel like there aren't many places to meet people these days.
うん、出会う場所は今あんまりないなって感じです
Not so much, I guess you don't need a special man?
あんまりじゃあ、特別男いらないみたいな?
Isn't that so?
そう でもない?
Not really, but it feels like it.
というわけでもないけど、って感じです
That's right.
そう なんだ
Well, I'm going to go to the chisel, but.
え、ノミとか行くんですよ、でも
Ah, but I do go sometimes.
あ、でもたまに行きますよ
Do you ever get called out to people like that?
そういうとこで声かけられたりしない?
Well, sometimes.
えー、たまに
Something like a pick-up.
ナンパみたいなやつ
Well, what do you do about that?
え、そういうのはどうするの?
If someone calls out to you.
声かけられたら
Eh, but I can't keep up.
えー、でもついていかないですね
That's quite a bit.
結構あれだな
Eh, maybe later?
え、後日とか?
Even if there is no such place.
その場はなくても
I don't have that place, so I go, but we only occasionally communicate and exchange things.
その場はないから行くでも、 連絡とか交換とかはたまにや
I will.
ります
There isn't much development.
あ んまり発展することないですね
Well, I guess I'll try drinking it again later.
え、だって後日なんか飲み直そうとかさ、
Let's have some fun or something, huh, haven't you heard from me?
なんか遊ぼうとかさ、 え、連絡とかないの?
I exchanged it.
って交換したら
I'm going.
行きます
Huh, is that going?
え、それは行くの?
Two people didn't go.
二人行かなかったり
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Wait, are you like a regular celebrity right now?
え、今固定のセブレみたいにいるの?
There is no fixed one, there is no fixed one.
固定はいないですね、固定は
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなの?
Eh, then maybe you won't do it at all?
え、じゃあ全然しないってこともしかして?
Well, I guess not much.
え、あんまりしないかな
That's terrible.
やばいね
Eh, it looks like you've contacted me anyway?
え、それでもしかして連絡してきたみたいな?
That might be the case too.
それもあるかも
Oh, there's one thing.
あ、ワンチャンあるんだ
Great, that's awesome.
いいね、やばいね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
No, but it turned out to be really cute,
いや、でもなんかすげえ可愛くなってて、
I was surprised today.
今日びっくりした
Oh, I'm happy.
え、嬉しい
You cut the paper.
紙切ったよね
Wasn't it longer?
なんかもっと長くなかった?
Huh, how many centimeters did you cut?
え、何センチくらい切ったの?
Ah, but that was probably it.
あ、でも多分これくらいだったんで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよ
20 centimeters?
20センチ?
15 centimeters?
15センチ?
Eh, why did you drop that relationship?
え、なんでそんな関係落としたの?
I thought I'd do a little image chain.
ちょっとイメチェーンしようかなと思って
Nice, but also short.
いいね、でもショートも
Short doesn't mean it's extremely short though.
ショートってめちゃくちゃ短いってわけじゃないけど
I?
僕?
No, short hair shows the outline of your face.
いや、ショートって顔の輪郭とか出るじゃん
I thought only beautiful women looked good.
美人しか似合わないって思ってたけど
Because she's beautiful.
美人だから
happy.
嬉しい
Oh, so you're not playing around?
え、じゃああんま遊んでないの?
I agree.
そうですね
Yeah.
うん
Oh, I miss you so much.
え、寂しき
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
So you're calling me because you're lonely?
だから寂しきから連絡してきたってことか
Nice, but.
いいね、でもね
But a man who seems like he'll come if I call him,
でもなんか呼んだら来てくれそうな男の人、
That's right.
いそうじゃん
Why did you contact me?
なんでなんか連絡してきてくれたの?
Eh, but I remembered it all the time, so I couldn't forget, so I contacted you.
え、でもずっと覚えてたんで、忘れられなかったから連絡
I did.
しました
I'm really happy.
め っちゃ嬉しい
Wow, he's such a good kid.
やばい、めちゃくちゃいい子じゃん
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
What have you been up to lately?
おなにとかはしてるの最近?
I mean recently.
最近っていうか
Yeah, but sometimes that too.
え、でもたまにそれも
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm sorry, but I had to ask you something like that all of a sudden.
ごめんね、急にそんなこと聞いちゃって
No, I don't play at all,
いや、なんかさ、全然遊んでないし、
People like.
みたいな人は
surely.
確かに
Alone.
一人で
That's terrible.
やばいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's no good.
ダメだよね
No, but I'm really, really happy.
いや、でも本当めっちゃ、すごい嬉しいよ
It’s been a long time since we met.
久々会えて
I wanted to meet you.
会いたかったし
Can I go sometimes?
たまに行っていい?
I'm a bit embarrassed, so what should I do while wearing this?
ちょっと俺、恥ずかしいからさ、これ被りながら何だったらいい?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
Yeah, but how often do you actually do it?
え、でも実際どれくらいしないの?
Well, I wonder how much.
えー、どれくらいだろう
Do you remember anything recently?
最近なんか覚えてる?
Naughty.
エッチ
Yeah, but I think it was quite a while ago.
えー、でも結構前だと思います
Seriously?
マジ?
Is this your boyfriend?
これは彼氏?
At that time, he was my boyfriend.
その時は彼氏
It's really good.
めちゃくちゃいいじゃん
cute.
かわいい
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
cute.
かわいい
Really.
めっちゃ
Oh, did that grow too?
あ、あれも成長した?
Maybe.
もしかして
Super smooth.
超すべすべ
That's terrible.
やばいね
Oh, take a look at my butt too.
あ、ちょっとお尻も見て
nice.
いいね
So nice.
めっちゃ素敵
This is also dangerous.
これもし、やばいね
Seriously.
マジ
nice.
いいね
No, I really like the style.
いや、ほんとスタイルいいね
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
Awesome.
すっごい
Oh, are you doing any muscle training?
え、なんか筋トレとかしてるの?
Eh, I haven't.
え、してない
What, you haven't done that and are maintaining it?
え、してなくてそれ維持してるの?
diet.
ダイエット
Isn't your skin white?
肌白くない?
amazing.
すごい
There's something I'd like you to wear today.
今日さ、なんか着て欲しいやつがあるんだけどさ
Yeah.
うん
Did you come out?
出てきてて?
I'd like you to take a look.
ちょっと見て欲しいんだけど
That's amazing, kind of.
すごいな、なんかさ
Eh, what is that?
え、なにそれ?
Dark bear.
あくま
It's already like a dark bear.
もうあくまみたいな
No, I think it looks really good on you.
いや、めっちゃ似合うかなと思って
cute.
かわいい
I just bought some.
ちょっと買っちゃったんだよね
Try it on.
着てみて
So, can I have you try it on here?
じゃあちょっと、ここで着てもらっていいですか?
But I really like the style.
でもめちゃくちゃスタイルいいね
Seriously.
マジで
terrible.
やばい
This one is a bit risqué.
ちょっと結構際どいやつだから、これ
It might be a bit dangerous.
ちょっとやばいかも
Oh, but is that underwear?
え、でもそれ下着?
Why don't you take off your underwear?
下着脱いでじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
I can help you if you don't understand.
ちょっと分からなかったら手伝おうかな
Yeah.
うん
Hey, have you ever worn something like this?
え、こういうの着たことある?
Cosplay.
コスプレ
Even in cosplay, this is quite exposed...
コスプレでもこれ結構露出...
Yeah, it's racy.
ね、際どい
It's a real thing.
際際のやつだよね
What size?
どうサイズか?
Looks okay.
大丈夫そう
It's okay because you're thin.
痩せてるから大丈夫だよね
She's an angel, but I think she'll turn into a dark bear today.
天使なんだけど、ちょっと今日あくまになってもらうかなと思
That's it.
って
No, I like it.
いや、 いいね
Very erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロー
It's fine after all.
やっぱいいよ
I'm glad I brought it.
持ってきてよかったわ
Isn't this your back?
これ背中じゃない?
perhaps.
多分
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみて
Probably yes, yes.
多分そうだよ、そう
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Is it above normal?
普通上かな?
Let's put it here, then.
こっちにしとこう、じゃあ
I don't really understand though.
ちょっと分かんないけど
Did you do it?
できた?
whole body?
全身?
Nice, very messed up.
いいね、めちゃくちゃ
So cute.
すげーかわいい
That's a little behind.
それもうちょっと後ろくるって
Too nice.
素敵すぎる
Nice ass.
いいね、お尻
Wow, my legs are a little wide.
やば、ちょっと足広い
Damn it, it's so dark.
やばい、こんなあくまだったら
It would be nice if you could come out for a moment.
ちょっと出てきてもらってもいいね
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
It looks great on you.
すごい似合ってる
How do you feel about it coming?
どう来た感想なんか?
Cute though.
かわいいけど
It's disgusting.
気悪い
That's good.
それがいいんだよ
Then sit down.
じゃあ座って
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロ
It's so wet.
すごいビチョビチョだよ
Expand yourself a little.
ちょっと自分で広げて
oh yeah.
そうそう
I want you to breathe a lie.
嘘を吸ってほしい
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
The house next door is so close.
めっちゃ近いから、隣の家が
it hurts.
痛い
Just lie down and stay there.
寝乗ってそのまま
I'm losing my voice.
声抜いてる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's very close to the outside.
めっちゃ外近いね
It's dangerous to raise your shoulders.
肩上げてやばい
That's how it works.
それで動いてる
A little more front mirror.
もうちょっと前鏡
Yes, look at the camera.
そう、カメラ見て